{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990972638","data":{"timestamp":" 947990972638"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990977213","data":{"timestamp":" 947990977213"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990978767","data":{"timestamp":" 947990978767"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990983086","data":{"timestamp":" 947990983086"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990984636","data":{"timestamp":" 947990984636"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990986703","data":{"timestamp":" 947990986703"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990988264","data":{"timestamp":" 947990988264"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990990151","data":{"timestamp":" 947990990151"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990991717","data":{"timestamp":" 947990991717"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990993732","data":{"timestamp":" 947990993731"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990995288","data":{"timestamp":" 947990995287"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990999239","data":{"timestamp":" 947990999239"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991000802","data":{"timestamp":" 947991000802"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991004810","data":{"timestamp":" 947991004810"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991006365","data":{"timestamp":" 947991006365"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991010535","data":{"timestamp":" 947991010535"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991012099","data":{"timestamp":" 947991012099"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991015299","data":{"timestamp":" 947991015299"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991016858","data":{"timestamp":" 947991016858"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991021119","data":{"timestamp":" 947991021118"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991022699","data":{"timestamp":" 947991022698"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991024729","data":{"timestamp":" 947991024728"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991024828","data":{"timestamp":" 947991024828"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 7faacbf4-8953-4f0d-be4f-7c0a41237f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991035858","data":{"timestamp":" 947991035858"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 71270bfc-e31c-49a0-8700-f4fab901b3e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-1-10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991043497","data":{"timestamp":" 947991043497"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 71270bfc-e31c-49a0-8700-f4fab901b3e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-1-10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991048695","data":{"timestamp":" 947991048694"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 71270bfc-e31c-49a0-8700-f4fab901b3e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_2-11-13"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991056036","data":{"timestamp":" 947991056036"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 71270bfc-e31c-49a0-8700-f4fab901b3e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_2-11-13"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991087465","data":{"timestamp":" 947991087465"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 71270bfc-e31c-49a0-8700-f4fab901b3e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_10-5-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991094103","data":{"timestamp":" 947991094103"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 71270bfc-e31c-49a0-8700-f4fab901b3e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-0-11"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991101337","data":{"timestamp":" 947991101337"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 71270bfc-e31c-49a0-8700-f4fab901b3e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-1-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991109392","data":{"timestamp":" 947991109391"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 71270bfc-e31c-49a0-8700-f4fab901b3e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-10-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991110062","data":{"timestamp":" 947991110062"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_054918"," gameId":" 71270bfc-e31c-49a0-8700-f4fab901b3e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-10-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}